buyii.com.au 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy for Buyii.com.au

Buyii cares about your privacy and takes it very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the Buyii website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers Buyii’s treatment of personal information that Buyii gathers when you are on the Buyii website and when you use Buyii services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Buyii does not own or control, or to individuals that Buyii does not employ or manage.

### What personal information about users does Buyii collect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you.

Buyii collects personally identifying information during the registration process, including name, email address, address, gender, store preferences etc. Buyii also may, on occasion collect user preference information (such as items clicked from emails), to be used for internal research purposes. We may also store information users knowingly provide; such as feedback forms, suggestions, and emails to the Buyii website.Buyii may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, email and web design optimizations, new features, and editorial and feedback purposes. Information entered may be aggregated across all users in order to determine and target demographics for marketing and advertising purposes.

All user information stored by Buyii is considered confidential and will not be shared with outside parties. Buyii may share aggregated results of preferences for all users for marketing and advertising purposes.  
If you object to such use for any reason, you can either let us know by sending us feedback, or you can unsubscribe from the Buyii email service.

### What about cookies?

Buyii uses cookies to provide you with a better experience. These cookies and allow us to increase your security by storing your section ID and a way of monitoring single user access. This aggregate, non-personal information is collated and provided to Buyii to assist in analysing the usage of the site. 

### Will Buyii share any of the information it receives?

 Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below.

 Protection of Buyii and others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Buyii, our employees, our users, or others.

 With your consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out.  

### Is information about me secure?

 Your Buyii account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by logging off once you have finished using a shared computer.

### Links to Other Sites

Buyii uses links to guide you toward valuable products, services and editorial. We are not responsible for any content that appears on these sites, nor do we endorse them. For questions about these sites, please consult their individual privacy policies.

### How do I Unsubscribe?

 To unsubscribe, click on the unsubscribe link in any Buyii email. You will be taken to a confirmation page. Click on the confirm link and you will be unsubscribed. You can also unsubscribe or change your email frequency anytime by Logging In and going to your 'My Account' settings page.

### Modifications to Privacy Policy

Buyii reserves the right to change this policy from time to time, however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. Please note that continued access of Buyii will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.
